

## **CONTACT ME**

+94 772528674

s.sajanthini98@gmail.com

in <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/sajanthini-satkunarasa">https://www.linkedin.com/in/sajanthini-satkunarasa</a>

Aanatha Road Manipay, Jaffna

## **EDUCATION**

JAN 2019 – APRIL 2023 University of Colombo, Sri Lanka,

Faculty of Science.

Course – Industrial Statistics & Mathematical Finance Bachelor of Science Honors in Science and Management

#### 2009 - 2017

J/Manipay Ladies College G.C.E Advance Level: Physical Science (A2B) Z-Score: 1.4396

## SOFT SKILLS

Team work, Leadership, Decision making, Problem solving, Selflearning, Communication, Analytics, Presentation

## **COURSE MODULES**

Introduction to Survey Design, Basic Statistic Inference, Design & Analysis of Industrial Experiment, Applied Statistical Model, Introduction to Probability & Distribution, Data Mining, HR Management, Quality & Project Management, Operation Research, Advanced Database System, Risk Management, Statistic in Practice, Business Economics and Econometrics, Fundamentals of software engineering.

# Sajanthini Satkunarasa

## Post Graduate

#### **PROFILE**

I am a self-motivated, independent, and hardworking final-year undergraduate student specializing in B.Sc. Honors in Science and Management. Programming languages stimulate my interest more. I want to advance my career by working in software engineering.

## WORK EXPERIENCE -

Job position here

2022 - 2023

## **OneData Software Solutions**

I worked in web development at OneData Software Solutions Private Limited, From 15 November 2022 to 31 January 2023.

As an outsourcer, I worked on SYNAPSYS LTD's wallet project, from 01 February 2023 to present

## **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Python, HTML, CSS, PHP, IBM SPSS, MY SQL, R, Java Script, C#, Minitab, NumPy, Pandas, MATLAB, Power BI, Octave, MS Office, Re-act, .Net, Angular

## **PROJECT**

Implementation of drink dispenser using c# <a href="https://github.com/Sajanthini/DrinkDiapenserProject">https://github.com/Sajanthini/DrinkDiapenserProject</a>

Calculator develop by using python code <a href="https://github.com/Sajanthini/calculator">https://github.com/Sajanthini/calculator</a>

Employee Management System <a href="https://github.com/Sajanthini/Api-sample-front-end.git">https://github.com/Sajanthini/Api-sample-front-end.git</a> <a href="https://github.com/Sajanthini/Api-sample-back-end.git">https://github.com/Sajanthini/Api-sample-back-end.git</a>

## **LANGUAGES**

Tamil: Native proficiency

Sinhala: Limited working proficiency English: Professional working Proficiency

## REFERENCES

Dr.A.A. Sunethra Senior Lecturer - Department of Statistics, University of Colombo. Colombo, Sri Lanka Tel: +94112590111 Email: sunethra@stat.cmb.ac.lk